Okay. Well, here we go. We'll bring up a
new terminal. We will go uh we will just
run scripts slashstart_mac.sh.
Um, okay. Here we go. Let's give this a
shot. It says it's running. Let's go and
take a look. Let's see if it's actually
uh running. Bring this up. Here is the
browser window.
Let's see what we get. Okay, it's
working.
It's working. The portfolio isn't empty,
but that's because it's remembered the
data from the uh uh from from the last
portfolio. That's something. Uh wow. I
don't That's of course because we had
that database directory locally. Okay.
This looks really cool. Uh what do you
think? I think this is probably a better
display. It's got a lot in common. Um
all right, let's uh It's amazing that it
looks so similar, actually. So, how do
we add a ticker to to um to this? Well,
let's let's just uh buy uh four Apple sh
three Apple shares. Press buy. There we
go. Three got onto the list right here.
And Apple appeared right here. Okay,
that's nice. And that's the portfolio.
And the cash is changing. Let's try this
again. Let's go for for Meta. And let's
get uh 10 Meta and press buy. I saw the
cash come right the way down. Portfolios
come all the way up. and meta is now a
big part of the portfolio, but this
isn't actually showing in different
colors yet. So, the heat map looks a bit
inferior, but generally speaking, it is
working. We'll give it that. This is
pretty cool, I have to say. Uh, what
just happened to Amazon? I'm not sure,
but uh in we will come back in a sec and
try out the AI assistant. Okay, so I'm
going to say, "Hi there."
And it's thinking, "Hello, how can I
assist you with your portfolio today?"
Uh, I'm going to say, uh, um, I'd like
to add, um, let's see, what should we
add? Let's add IBM to the watch list.
Okay, it's thinking.
Still thinking.
IBM has been added to your watch list.
And it has. IBM is on the watch list.
This is working. Okay. Uh let's now say
okay uh I'd like to uh buy one share of
IBM
and sell
five shares of Meta.
Let's see what happens. Let's see what
happens. Your one and we want Meta to go
down to five in our portfolio right
here. It's thinking over here.
We're not getting the the trademark
speed from Cerebrass, but there we go.
It did its thing. It executed uh buy and
sell and I see that IBM is up to one and
Meta is down to five. It is working and
I see our portfolio updating down there
and that's pretty cool. Uh so I would
say this is this is really nice. Uh this
chart here is odd. I'm not sure why
we're not seeing something there. It's
funny that we had the same problem the
other UI as well. It's meant to be
showing uh Apple, I guess. And this
portfolio isn't highlighting in colors
this heat map the the way that the other
one did. But otherwise, I would say this
is pretty impressive. The chat is
working. This is working really nicely.
That just looks terrific. And generally
speaking, it's working. It's uh I I'm um
I'm not sure which one I give the edge.
Probably the other one. Actually, I
think I give Claude agents teams a
slight one one step ahead of this, but
it's pretty impressive. Let's face it.
And I've also I just dug into the code a
bit to see whether it was using our
skill to call Cerebrass. And I've
noticed some interesting stuff here. And
the code that it's got here is that it
is using Cerebrass, but it's not using
our code. It is using light LLM as well.
So it seems that it's read our skill,
but it's taken it in a different
direction. It's using a different
approach for structured outputs. It may
be this sometimes happens when it does
what we suggest and then hits some sort
of a bug. And the way that it fixes the
bug is to sort of rewrite and do things
differently. So I'm speculating that
something like that happened. So it
still stayed true to to sending it to
Cerebras, but it's also doing some
different things to perhaps after
encountering a bug. But generally
speaking, I would say this is pretty
solid for a first implementation. Even
if it didn't take a while, I'm pretty
happy with the results. And as a final
step, we should check into GitHub. Let's
just see. I know it's been taking uh um
commits as we go. So, a lot has already
been committed. There's just a little
bit left to go. Some of the the most
recent stuff with the uh uh Oh, that's
weird that it's got a no modules not get
ignored from the test directory. Um we
would want to do that. That seems like a
bit of a mistake. Um and um yeah, so so
uh I will now check this all into git.
So, we've got it nice and tight and then
I will see you for the wrap. Wait a
second. I couldn't resist. Before we
have the rap, I had to bring up the two
user interfaces side by side. And it's
kind of hard cuz neither of them does
well when it's squashed horizontally.
But this is the first one we built. This
is the one that took half an hour and
used agent used um agent teams from
Claude. Uh and uh it had this this
slight janky problem here. It also has
this problem that it can't seem to to
get the prices of things that aren't on
the watch list. That seems like a bug,
but the UI is really nice and I love the
way it does this. Uh, and then um, yeah,
I I think it looks very professional and
it hasn't fallen prey to that problem
where these LLMs tend to have purple
backgrounds to all of their UIs. Uh, the
one that that took all of the hours. Uh,
the 5hour alternative is this one. It
looks very similar. I think that it's
it's failed on the heat map isn't
colored in in the way that the original
one was. um and that this isn't quite as
dramatic, but it hasn't got the same
bug. It is able to deal with with new
things that isn't on the watch list and
it's able to to handle things better,
able to add to the watch list as we saw
and still have prices for things that
get added. So, from that point of view,
maybe it did a little bit better from a
quality point of view. Uh but I also I
really like the uh the original one,
too. So, I don't know. You It's your
call. Of course, it's your call. put it
in the chat in Udemy which one you think
is better. Uh but but for me, I'm going
with the first one. Actually, I I think
that that despite the defects, which I
think I could I could tell it to fix
them pretty quickly. And the fact that
it got the whole thing done in in half
an hour, uh already speaks volumes to
me. But two beautiful products. It's
super fun to see them side by side. And
I hope you like that. And now I will see
you for the rap. Well, what a day it's
been. I told you it would be a great day
at a roller coaster. I wasn't I have to
admit I wasn't expecting how much I was
signing up for. For you, it's just been
like an hour. For me, it's been a whole
day of toiling with GSD. I I understand
why people love it. I see that when it's
taking on a really big project,
especially if you're willing to run it
in YOLO mode and just leave it be, then
it's clearly very, very diligent. I
mean, honestly, when I saw it like going
backwards and forwards over confirming
and double-checking and triple-checking
that the tests were passing, it was
clearly very thorough indeed. I see why
it works well, but it's it's it's a a
lot of time spent and and a lot of
tokens spent as well. Uh so, so we we
really saw those two sides of the
spectrum. We saw the new clawed agent
teams and how it's able to be very
dynamic. And then we saw the more
regimented, more strict orchestration in
GSD. And I think we enjoyed two fabulous
results as as a result of that. And uh
yeah, I hope you enjoyed that. And then
tomorrow we should have a fitting
finale. I can't wait to show you what I
got in store for you. With that, that
brings us to 93% of the way along. We've
only got 7% left and it's all tomorrow.